Office of Publications Records UA012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Buildings and grounds, 1908 -- 2009; 1963 -- 2002; UA012.001; 3.7 Linear Feet
  - Medford Campus, 1970; UA012.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Memorial steps, Eaton Hall, Miller Hall and ROTC building. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus, 1970; UA012.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Memorial steps/Anderson and Robinson, Miner Hall, construction of Tisch Library. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus, 1960; UA012.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Dewick MacPhie, labratory and general campus. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus, 1970; UA012.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of night Library, Chapel, Ballou. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus, 1960 -- 1976; UA012.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of Barnum, general campus (airview), events. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus, 1961; UA012.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of President's House, tennis courts, Goddard
  - Medford Campus, 1977 -- 1989; UA012.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of Paige hall and Memorial Steps
  - Medford Campus "Along the Row", 1961 -- 1973; UA012.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of Dearborn Gate and general scenery
  - Medford Campus (Betty Weiant), 1952 -- 1970; UA012.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of tress, winter scenes, Goddard Chapel. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus (Betty Weiant), 1960; UA012.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of spring and winter scenes. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus- buildings, 1960; UA012.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of Gate, Ballou, Goddard (exterior and Interior), Eaton, Fletcher School, Braker, Pearson, Cohen, Strattou, Bookstore, Sweet (ROTC), Dewick, Couzens, Miner + P, Memorial Steps, Broy Lab, Carmichael, Miller, Packard and East. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus- buildings, 1960; UA012.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of the cannon, Fletcher School, Carmichael, Miller, Packard and East, general campus scenery. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus- interiors & exteriors, 1960; UA012.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of the labratory interior, dorm interior, lounge, Cohen interior, Goddard, fraternity, Dewick, Fletcher, Academic quad, Paige Hall, Charmichael, construction. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus in the snow (Betty Weiant), 1970; UA012.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of winter scenery/ snow sculptures. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus in the snow (Betty Weiant), 1970; UA012.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of winter scenery, shoveled paths. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus- New Construction, 1993; UA012.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
    This folder contains pictures of Olin renderings, unknown building
  - Medford Campus- New Construction, 1993; UA012.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
    This folder contains pictures of Olin, Aidekman
  - Medford Campus- Snow and Sunset, 1977; UA012.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of Goddard exterior and interior, West hall, sunset and snow scenery
  - Medford Campus- Spring scnes (Betty Weiant), 1951 -- 1954; UA012.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of spring flora and general scenery
  - Medford Campus- signage, skyline, 1961 -- 1986; UA012.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of Boston skyline from Tufts campus, students, signs, gate
  - Medford Campus- Winter, 1960; UA012.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of library steps, winter Paige Hall, winter Ballou, winter bookstore, winter Bracker, winter East, winter Gate, winter Fletcher. Date is approximate
  - Medical and Dental, 1960; UA012.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of interior and exterior of the Medical and Dental buildings. Date is approximate
  - Medical and Dental, 1960; UA012.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Memorial Stairs, 1961; UA012.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of Memorial stairs.
  - Memorial Stairs/Sign, 1960; UA012.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of Memorial stairs, signs, and Tufts brochures. Date is approximate
  - Miller, 1961; UA012.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Miller Hall
  - Miller, 1961; UA012.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Miller, 1986; UA012.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Miller Hall with students
  - Miner Hall, Arch, 1986; UA012.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Miner Hall and archway. Date as marked
  - Miner-Paige-Crane, 1961 -- 1973; UA012.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Miner Hall, Paige, Crane.
  - Miner-Paige-Crane, Fischer arcade, Starkweather Gate, 1961 -- 1973; UA012.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Miner Hall, Paige, Crane, Fischer arcade, Starkweather gate. Date is approximate
  - Misc BLDGS etc, 1961 -- 1989; UA012.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Latin Way, Hillside, bookstore, Wren, Lewis, Fletcher, Bromfield-Pearson and others. Interior of Barnum, locker room.
  - Mugar, 1985; UA012.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Mugar hall
  - Outdoors, 1977 -- 1985; UA012.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of general Tufts campus/students
  - Outside (no peeps), 1989; UA012.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of exterior Paige hall, Miner hall, memorial steps
  - Packard Hall, 1990; UA012.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of exterior Packard Hall. Date is approximate
  - Packard & West, 1908 -- 1961; UA012.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of exterior Packard Hall and West hall.
  - Packard, West and East, 1961; UA012.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of exterior Packard Hall, West hall, East hall.
  - Seasonal, 1977; UA012.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of Fall foliage, winter Academic quad and Charmicael
  - signage, UA012.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
    This folder contains pictures of signs: Tufts, College of Engineering, Sivanus Packard society
  - Skyline, 1986; UA012.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of Boston/Medford/Somerville skyline from Tufts Campus
  - Skyline Campus, 1986; UA012.001.004.00042 (Box 4)
    This folder contains slides of Tufts Campus (Medford)
  - Slides from Breed-Color, UA012.001.004.00043 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of gates, academic quad
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1955; UA012.001.004.00044 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of gates, float, Miller Hall. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1955; UA012.001.004.00045 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of gates, Dewick/Bush, Miller Hall. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00046 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Hodgdon, Cousins, Miller Hall. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1955; UA012.001.004.00047 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of floats/parade. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00048 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Packard/West, Miller, Lane. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00049 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Charmicael, Miller, Lane, Labratory. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00050 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Sweet, boiler, Miller, Paige/Miner. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00051 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of bookstore, Memorial Steps, Miller, Barnum Museum garden. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00052 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Eaton, Anderson/Robinson, Miller/Charmicael. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00053 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Anderson/Robinson, Miller, Ballou. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00054 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Anderson/Robinson, Memorial Steps, Hodgdon. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00055 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of winter/summer academic quad, library. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00056 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Ballou, Goddard, Lane, others. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00057 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of boiler, Goddard, Hodgdon, Miller/Charmicael. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00058 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Ballou/Goddard. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00059 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Eaton, Charmicael, Miller. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00060 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of academic quad, Charmicael, Miller. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00061 (Box 4)
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00062 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Eaton, Charmicael, Ballou/Goddard. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00063 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Eaton, Charmicael/Miller, bookstore. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00064 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Ballou, Charmicael, Sweet. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00065 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Eaton, Miller, Hodgdon, academic quad. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00066 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Ballou and cannon, Paige/Miner. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00067 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Ballou and cannon, gate/Charmicael, Miller, Packard/West. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00068 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Ballou, Goddard. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00069 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of Charmicael, Paige/Miner hall, library steps, Goddard, views. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1970; UA012.001.004.00070 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of students, lab interiors, library roof, Anderson/Robinson. Date is approximate
  - Slides from Breed- Color, 1960; UA012.001.004.00071 (Box 4)
    This folder contains photos of academic quad, Ballou, Goddard. Date is approximate
  - Sweet Hall + ROTC (1 of 2), 1960; UA012.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of Sweet Hall. Date is approximate
  - Sweet Hall + ROTC (2 of 2), 1961; UA012.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of Sweet Hall.
  - Tisch, 1990; UA012.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of exterior Tisch, figure head. Date is approximate
  - Tisch details, 1990; UA012.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of exterior Tisch. Date is approximate
  - Tisch Library, 1986; UA012.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of Ballou Hall, student with books.
  - Tisch Library, 1996; UA012.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of exterior Tisch library
  - Tisch Library Inside (1 of 9), 1996; UA012.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Tisch Library: students on computers
  - Tisch Library Inside (2 of 9), 1996; UA012.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Tisch Library: students on computers, Reference & Information desk
  - Tisch Library Inside (3 of 9), 1996; UA012.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Tisch Library: students studying
  - Tisch Library Inside (4 of 9), 1996; UA012.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Tisch Library: class with computers
  - Tisch Library Inside (5 of 9), 1996; UA012.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Tisch Library Inside (6 of 9), 1996; UA012.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Tisch Library: Reference and Information desk
  - Tisch Library Inside (7 of 9), 1996; UA012.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Tisch Library: reserve and request desk
  - Tisch Library Inside (8 of 9), 1996; UA012.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Tisch Library Inside (9 of 9), 1996; UA012.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Tisch Library: renderings of Tisch Library
  - Tisch Media Center (1 of 4), 1995; UA012.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Tisch Media Center: reception desk, woman watching video. Date is approximate
  - Tisch Media Center (2 of 4), 1995; UA012.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Tisch Media Center: woman watching video. Date is approximate
  - Tisch Media Center (3 of 4), 1995; UA012.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Tisch Media Center and library: woman watching video, students studying. Date is approximate
  - Tisch Media Center (4 of 4), 1995; UA012.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Tisch Media Center: reception desk. Date is approximate
  - Tisch Outside, 1980; UA012.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of exterior Tisch Library. Date is approximate
  - Tisch Outside, 1990; UA012.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Tisch Outside, 1990; UA012.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Tisch Outside, 1990; UA012.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of exterior Tisch Library, students on roof. Date is approximate
  - Tisch Outside, 1990; UA012.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Tufts - Medford Campus, 1965; UA012.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of winter scenes, interior Goddard chapel, skyline, sunset, statues, Ballou, Chemistry building, Charmichael.
  - Tufts - Medford Campus, 1956 -- 1986; UA012.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of Commencement 1986 & 1976, academic quad, skyline, Charmichael
  - Tufts - Medford Campus, 1965; UA012.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of Wren, Dewick, Miller, Houston, Dana labratory, winter academic quad, chemisty building
  - Tufts - Medford Campus, 1965; UA012.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of winter Goddard, Fletcher, East Hall, Wren, winter/spring scenery/academic quad, skyline, Eaton, chemistry building
  - Tufts - Medford Campus, 1965; UA012.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of Ballou, Memorial steps, Goddard at night, Fletcher, chemistry building, Charmichael, Miner hall, academic quad
  - Tufts Program and signs, 1961; UA012.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of Tufts signs and renderings of campus buildings and others
  - Wessell, 1977 -- 1980; UA012.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of exterior of Wessell library, and students on roof
  - Wessell, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Wessell, 1985 -- 1987; UA012.001.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Wessell, 1984 -- 1986; UA012.001.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Wessell, 1985; UA012.001.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Wessell, 1985; UA012.001.005.00036 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of Wessell court, and students on roof. Date is approximate
  - Wessell, 1965; UA012.001.005.00037 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of Wessell court, Wessell interior, Goddard chapel.
  - Wessell Library, 1965; UA012.001.005.00038 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of Wessell court, Goddard chapel from Wessell roof.
  - Wessell Library, 1965; UA012.001.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - Wessell Library and Medrod campus in bloom, 1965 -- 1979; UA012.001.005.00040 (Box 5)
    This folder contains slides of interior Wessell library, spring scenery.
  - West Hall, 1980; UA012.001.005.00041 (Box 5)
    This folder contains negatives of exterior West Hall, man and woman walking. Date is approximate
  - Campus 98, 1984 -- 1998; UA012.001.023.00001 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    This folder contains slides of students walking around the grounds. Most slides depict students in Spring.
  - Campus Fall, 1975 -- 1985; UA012.001.023.00002 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    This folder contains slides of students walking around the grounds. Most slides depict students in fall.
  - Campus Signs, 1964 -- 1995; UA012.001.023.00003 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    Dates are approximate. This folder contains slides of students looking at campus signs, mostly map of Tufts campus. There is also a slide of a 1926 photograph of "The Rez" and a picture of the sign for A Center For All Faiths.
  - Experimental College Signs, 1980; UA012.001.023.00004 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    This folder contains images of signs for the Experimental College, Tufts Mountain Club, and Barnum 2nd Floor Corridor at Barnum's 100th.
  - Fall foliage scenes [1], 1985 -- 1989; UA012.001.023.00005 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    Photographs by Paula Lerner.
  - Fall foliage scenes [2], 1980 -- 1986; UA012.001.023.00006 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    Most slides show fall foliage, but one slide of Campus Directory and one of Jumbo Day parade.
  - Fall foliage scenes [3], 1977; UA012.001.023.00007 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    Photographs by Lynn McLaren.
  - Fall foliage scenes [4], 1984 -- 1987; UA012.001.023.00008 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    Photographs by Patty Lord.
  - Memorial Steps, 1989; UA012.001.023.00009 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
  - Miner Hall, 1985; UA012.001.023.00010 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    Photographs by Paula Lerner. Depict Memorial Steps.
  - Miner Hall, Ballou Hall, 1980 -- 1987; UA012.001.023.00011 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    Slides of various buildings around campus. Includes many images of Memorial Steps.
  - Spring scenes, 1980 -- 1998; UA012.001.023.00012 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    Dates are approximate. Also contains a couple of posed student photographs.
- Students, 1960 -- 2005; 1963 -- 2002; UA012.002; 3.7 Linear Feet
  This series contains photographs, slides, and negatives of Tufts University students from 1967 to 1999. Images include stock photography used in publications as well as candid shots of the academic and social lives of students. Shots are taken in a variety of locations, including classrooms, libraries, on campus grounds and around Boston. Some also depict specific students; Medical, Dental, Fletcher. This series contains a number of images used in admissions campaigns for the College of Arts & Sciences, as well as the Fletcher School.
  - Academic - indoor and outdoor, 1983 -- 1993; UA012.002.006.00022 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Includes a number of black and white photographs of students, mostly from the 1980s.
  - Academic settings [1 of 2], 1982 -- 1997; UA012.002.006.00023 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Contains photographic prints, negatives, and slides.
  - Academic settings [2 of 2], 1980 -- 1983; UA012.002.006.00024 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Contains a wide variety of photographs from a range of disciplines: Engineering, chemistry, liberal arts, dental school.
  - Photo file: Fletcher Students, 2004 -- 2005; UA012.002.006.00025 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Contains photographs of students Jonathan Lautze, Hassan Abbas, Emma Belcher, Kai Jellers, and Natalie Laidler-Kylander.
  - Photo file: Grad Arts and Science students, 2002; UA012.002.006.00026 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Contains photographs of individual students.
  - Graduate Students, 1998; UA012.002.006.00027 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Contains photographs of unidentified GSAS students in academic settings.
  - Medford students - dorm photos, 1998; UA012.002.006.00028 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Medford - students posed, 1986 -- 1993; UA012.002.006.00029 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Medford - sports, social, 1979 -- 1991; UA012.002.006.00030 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Contains photographic prints of student life. Some shots are academic, some depict Parent's Weekend events, others are of students out and about around Boston.
  - Photographs, handicapped students, 1977 -- 1988; UA012.002.006.00031 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Photographs, international students, 1980; UA012.002.006.00032 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Photographs, Medford students, 1974 -- 1993; UA012.002.006.00033 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Contains photographs of students engaged in generic academic activities, as well as scences involving chemistry, biology, as well as seagulls on the beach.
  - Photographs, minority students, 1979 -- 1991; UA012.002.006.00034 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Photographs, students outside, 1984 -- 1993; UA012.002.006.00035 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Portraits [1 of 2], 1981 -- 1990; UA012.002.006.00036 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Posed portraits of Tufts students.
  - Portraits [2 of 2], 1995; UA012.002.006.00037 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate. Contains photographs and negatives of posed Tufts students.
  - Portraits - Arts & Sciences case, 1995; UA012.002.006.00038 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Professor and Student, 1997; UA012.002.006.00039 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate. Unidentified students and professors posed.
  - Students - groups outside spring/summer, 1997 -- 1998; UA012.002.006.00040 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Photographs of Lisa Lay, sports photographer, J '86, and Javier Macaya, A '91.
  - Students - in class, 1986 -- 1998; UA012.002.006.00041 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Contains photographic prints and slides.
  - Students on campus, 1980s, 1985; UA012.002.006.00042 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate. Contains black and white photographs of campus with students walking and chatting the the shots.
  - Students outside, 1997 -- 1998; UA012.002.006.00043 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Students outside and social [1 of 2], 1979 -- 1982; UA012.002.006.00044 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    A collection of early photographs of students around campus, studying, chatting, and engaging in social activities.
  - Students outside and social [2 of 2], 1976 -- 1988; UA012.002.006.00045 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Students - single students outside, 1986 -- 1998; UA012.002.006.00046 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Students - walking/chat, 1998; UA012.002.006.00047 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Tufts students, 1999 -- 2002; UA012.002.006.00048 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Dates are approximate. Newer posed photographs of students around campus.
  - Students - groups outside spring/summer, 1997 -- 1998; UA012.002.006.00049 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    photographic print
  - Academic Scenes, 1980; UA012.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
    This folder contains negatives of students at computer, classroom. Date is approximate
  - Academic Scenes, 1996; UA012.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
    This folder contains negatives of students dining, classroom
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
    This folder contains envelope of pictures
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of three student poses
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of student posing